

Mauro Joel Bilotti

S. J. de Calasanz 1021 3, Buenos Aires, Argentina +54 11 21900876 | bilottimauro@gmail.com github.com/maurobilotti

in linkedin.com/in/mauro-bilotti-81291397

Objective

Information Systems Engineer with 8+ years of experience in different technologies and projects around the world. I'm an skilled .NET full-stack developer with strong engineering profile, interested in modern technologies and frameworks and software design.

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 01/10/1988Nationality: Argentina

Education

UTN FRBA (Universidad Tecnologica Nacional)
 Information Systems Engineer

2010 - 2020

Experience

Charles Taylor InsureTech Limited

Aug 2019 - Today

Software Engineer

Smartix project - InsureTech. Azure Cosmos DB (No-SQL), Angular 6, WCF - Web API, .NET Core 3.0, SQL Server 2018

Wheelzy
 Software Developer Engineer

May 2018 - Aug 2019

Software Developer Engineer

Development of different sites related with sales/purchase of cars in US. .NET Core + EF, AngularJS/Jquery, Bootstrap/CSS3. SQL Server 2016

 AON Software Developer Analyst Jul 2016 - May 2018

Development of applications and websites related to insurance. .NET MVC, Node.js, AngularJS, SQL Server 2012, Entity Framework, Web API services y SOAP Services, Bootstrap, Kentico CMS, ASP.NET Identity.

• Globant Jun 2015 - Jul 2016

.NET Developer Full-Stack

Developer analyst in different projects of Deloitte. AngularJS + Jquery, CSS+HTML5, ASP.NET MVC Web API, Entity Framework, SAP Services, RESTFUL Services, Unity (Dependency Injection), Open XML, API Blueprint, Unit Testing.

• **Hexacta** May 2014 - Jun 2015

.NET Developer Full-Stack

Developer in Bolloré-Ipaki project. Scrum methodology, Team Foundation Server (TFS) for general management of the tasks. ASP.NET MVC/Webforms, Jquery, CSS3, WCF services, SQL Server 2012, Entity Framework, PayPal REST API, iBatis framework.

• C-NET SRL Feb 2013 - Oct 2014

.NET Developer

Full stack developer in different projects related with engineering. WPF. Web app in ASP.NET MVC. Razor engine and Kendo UI framework for controls. HTML5, JQuery y CSS3. C/C++, Linux operating system.

• GlobalNews Feb 2011 - Feb 2013

.NET Developer

Developer in projects related with news processing. ASP.NET WebForms. Development of desktop applications on Windows Forms. LinqToSQL and ADO.NET as ORM. UML design. SVN for source control.

Projects

Smappio: Smart Electronic Wireless Sthethoscope

Wireless electronic sthetoscope developed by using Adafruit Feather Huzzah ESP32 module along with Adafruit I2S SPH0645 to capture body sounds (heart and lungs mainly). This project was presented in the congress CoNalISI 2018 in Mar Del Plata. (Source Code: github.com/maurobilotti/smappio)

· Sponsor.Online

SPONSOR.ONLINE is an early-stage digital marketplace that connects professional sports teams with suitable brands. The platform is growing fast and leading the digital way of sponsorship negotiation. I have worked in Product Development and Maintainance of the platform during the last 7 months on my free time. <u>Tech stack</u>: Laravel 7, Nuxt.js, MySQL, Go Lang, Google Cloud

· Stack Overflow member

Helping developers around the world with questions and answers. stackoverflow.com/users/2936486/mauro-bilotti

Language

- · English
- Portuguese
- Spanish

Reference

Mariano Rivera - "Baker Hughes"

Senior Software Engineer rivsoft@gmail.com +31 6 25574174

Maximilian Von Portatius - "Sponsor.Online"

Co-Founder and Managing Director mportatius@sponsor.online +41 79 139 39 99